tcpglobal.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

### Information about our Organization and Web site

We do not collect any personal data from our any of our visitors when they use our services except as necessary to complete a basic transaction. This site makes no descrimination as to age, gender or any other variable. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like TCPGlobal . We are based in USA .

Our principal activity is: Wholesale & Retail Automotive and Crafts Products

Our privacy policy covers TCPGlobal and its family of Web sites: 

Organization Name: | TCPGlobal  
---|---  
Address: | 6695 Rasha Street  
City, Zip: | San Diego, 92121-2241  
State: | CA  
Country: | USA  
Controller: | Len Savage  
Web Sites(s): | http://www.TriCityPaint.com  
http://www.AutoBodyDepot.net  
http://www.AutoColorLibrary.com  
http://www.SpraygunDepot.com  
http://www.AirBrush-Depot.com  
http://www.ProTanningSystems.com  
http://www.Turbo-Tan.com  
http://www.DetailSupplyDepot.com  
http://www.HOKPaint.com  
http://www.ProAutoTools.com  
  
#### Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access 

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

#### The services and links of our Web site 

Our Web site does include links to third party Web service providers. 

#### Automatic Collection of Information 

We do use cookies to store personal data but we do not link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

#### Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

#### Children's Privacy 

We do not collect any personal data from our any of our visitors when they use our services except as necessary to complete a basic transaction. This site makes no descrimination as to age, gender or any other variable.

#### Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

#### Confidentiality / Security 

We do not collect any personal data from our any of our visitors when they use our services except as necessary to complete a basic transaction. We have taken all reasonable steps to provide security from third party intrusion to your personal information.  

#### Access to the personal data we may hold about you 

We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services except as stated above.

#### Privacy Compliance 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. 

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are:

* voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure 

#### Self Assessment procedure

Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service | David Topp  
Network Administrator  
---|---  
URL | http://www.TCPGlobal.com  
Address | 6695 Rasha Street,   
San Diego, CA 92121  
Country | USA  
  
#### Privacy Support

### TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used 

#### Primary personal data/Business information

- | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
none | collected from public records or bodies  
none | collected from private organizations  
  
Primary personal data 

| Technical administration of the Web site  | Research &development  | Customer Administration | Marketing  | Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Name  | none | none | none | none | none  
Gender  | none | none | none | none | none  
Address  | none | none | none | none | none  
E-mail address  | none | none | none | none | none  
Phone/Fax number  | none | none | none | none | none  
other | none | none | none | none | none  
  
Business Information 

| Technical administration of the Web site  | Research & development  | Customer Administration  | Marketing  | Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Employer/organization  | none | none | none | none | none  
Job title  | none | none | none | none | none  
Address  | none | none | none | none | none  
E-mail address  | none | none | none | none | none  
Phone/Fax number  | none | none | none | none | none  
other | none | none | none | none | none  
  
#### Other personal details and profiling data

- | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
none | collected from public records or bodies  
none | collected from private organizations  
  
| Technical administration of the Web site  | Research & development  | Customer Administration  | Marketing  | Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Personal details  | none | none | none | none | none  
Physical description  | none | none | none | none | none  
Family characteristics  | none | none | none | none | none  
Education and skills  | none | none | none | none | none  
Life style or personal tastes  | none | none | none | none | none  
Financial resources  | none | none | none | none | none  
other | none | none | none | none | none  
  
#### Identifiers

- | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
none | collected from public records or bodies  
none | collected from private organizations  
  
| Technical administration of the Web site  | Research & development  | Customer Administration  | Marketing  | Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
On-line identifiers  | none | none | none | none | none  
Financial identifiers  | none | none | none | none | none  
identifiers assigned by Public bodies  | none | none | none | none | none  
Biometrics identifiers  | none | none | none | none | none  
other | none | none | none | none | none  
  
#### Specific Data

- | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
none | collected from public records or bodies  
none | collected from private organizations  
  
| Technical administration of the Web site  | Research & development  | Customer Administration  | Marketing  | Trading in personal data   
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Racial or ethnic origin  | none | none | none | none | none  
Political opinions  | none | none | none | none | none  
Religious or philosophical beliefs  | none | none | none | none | none  
Trade union membership  | none | none | none | none | none  
Health/Medical data  | none | none | none | none | none  
Sex life  | none | none | none | none | none  
Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor  | none | none | none | none | none  
other | none | none | none | none | none  
  
* * *

#### If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:

  | Contact 1  
---|---  
Name/designation : | Len Savage  
Department : | CTO  
Address : | 6695 Rasha Street, San Diego, CA  
Phone Number : | 858-909-2100  
Fax Number : | 858-909-2158  
Email address : |   
URL : | http://www.TCPGlobal.com  
  
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like TCPGlobal . We are based in USA .

Our principal activity is: Wholesale & Retail Automotive and Crafts Products

Our privacy policy covers TCPGlobal and its family of Web sites: 

** Organization Name: | TCPGlobal  
---|---  
Address: | 6695 Rasha Street  
City, Zip: | San Diego , 92121-2241  
State: | CA  
Country: | USA  
Controller: | Len Savage  
Web Sites(s): | http://www.TriCityPaint.com  
http://www.AutoBodyDepot.net  
http://www.AutoColorLibrary.com  
http://www.SpraygunDepot.com  
http://www.AirBrush-Depot.com  
http://www.ProTanningSystems.com  
http://www.Turbo-Tan.com  
http://www.DetailSupplyDepot.com  
http://www.HOKPaint.com  
http://www.ProAutoTools.com  
**
